mugasha.com 2009-11-20

# Privacy | Mugasha

## Privacy and Data Policy for Mugasha

Mugasha respects and values the privacy of our visitors and members. This privacy policy covers how Mugasha treats personal information collected and received.

**Last updated: September 26, 2008**

  1. **What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
This policy covers personal information including personally identifiable information about you like your name or email address. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties that Mugasha does not own or control, or to individuals that Mugasha does not control or manage. Note also that children under 13 are not permitted to use Mugasha. Therefore, Mugasha's privacy policy does not account for children's use of the site.
  2. **Links to Other Sites**  
Mugasha contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by Mugasha. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. 
  3. **Information Collection, Data Ownership and Use**  
Registered users of Mugasha own their personal information and data created as a result of using Mugasha.com. Mugasha.com will retain a non-exclusive license for the duration of time the user maintains data at Mugasha. In addition, for the duration of time users maintain data at Mugasha, they grant all users a commercial, non-exclusive reuse license to their publicly accessible data, created through the use of Mugasha, unless they choose options to limit the public distribution of their public data, such as "subscriptions",
